Guide to the Judy Blume Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Judy Blume papers
1952-2017
GEN MSS 1481
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
120.84
(128 boxes) + 1 roll
The Judy Blume papers consist of correspondence, manuscripts, printed material, audiovisual material, computer media, and personal and other papers documenting the life and work of American author Judy Blume.
Blume, Judy
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Acquired from various sources. For more information consult the appropriate curator.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research with the requirement that all users of the Papers must sign an agreement outlining specific conditions for use of the papers. These conditions are related to the presence of letters, documents and other materials that were written by children and other individuals to Ms. Blume on issues and topics that are personal to the writer. The Papers also contains copies of letters written by Ms. Blume responding to correspondence from her readers. These materials are in some cases catalogued as "correspondence" and in other cases are interspersed throughout the Papers.
Boxes 6, 92-103 (audiovisual material): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Boxes 23, 104-105, 119 (born digital): Restricted fragile material. Access copies of digital files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Arrangement
Organized into two subgroupings: October 2017 Acquisition and September 2018 Acquistion.
Judy Blume (1938-)
Judy Blume is an American author, educator, and advocate. She was born and raised in Elizabeth, New Jersey, before attending Boston University and New York University, where she earned a B.S. degree in Education in 1960. She is the author of over 30 books, most of which are written for children and young adults, dating from The One in the middle is the green kangaroo (1969) to In the unlikely event (2015).
Summary information is also available in the standard print and online biographical resources.
The following chronology provides dates for key events and selected publications:
1938 February 12 born Judy Sussman to Rudolph and Esther Sussman
1959 August 15 marries John Blume
1960 graduates from New York University with a B.S. degree in Education
1961 birth of son Randy Lee
1963 birth of son Andrew Lawrence
1969 publication of The one in the middle is the green kangaroo
1970 publication of Are you there God? It's me, Margaret, awarded Outstanding Book of the Year, New York Times
1971 publication of Freckle juice publication of Then again, maybe I won't
1972 publication of It's not the end of the world publication of Tales of a fourth grade nothing
1973 publication of Deenie
1974 publication of Blubber
1975 publication of Forever divorces John Blume
1976 marries Thomas A. Kitchens
1977 publication of Starring Sally J. Freedman as herself
1978 publication of Wifey divorces Thomas A. Kitchens
1980 publication of Superfudge, awarded Children's Choice Book Award
1981 publication of Tiger eyes founds KIDS Fund
1983 publication of Smart women
1984 publication of The pain and the great one
1986 publication of Letters to Judy: What your kids wish they could tell you, awarded the Literary Lions award, New York Public Library
1987 publication of Just as long as we're together marries George Cooper
1988 publication of Summer sisters
1990 publication of Fudge-a-mania
1993 publication of Here's to you, Rachel Robinson
1996 awarded the Margaret A. Edwards Award for Lifetime Achievement, American Library Association
2002 publication of Double Fudge
2004 awarded medal for Distinguished Contribution to American Letters, National Book Foundation
2015 publication of In the unlikely event
Scope and Contents
The Judy Blume papers consist of correspondence, drafts of writings, printed material, audiovisual material, computer media, and personal and other papers documenting the life and work of American author Judy Blume.
Correspondence is located throughout the collection and identified chiefly as professional, personal, and fan mail. Professional correspondence includes letters from publishers and literary and other organizations. Letters from fans are grouped together by date, by topic, and, in some cases, by individual correspondent.
Writings include manuscript drafts, proofs, and other materials. Multiple drafts can be found for many titles, including: Deenie (1973), Tiger eyes (1981), Smart women (1983), Just as long as we're together (1987), Fudge-a-mania (1990), Here's to you, Rachel Robinson (1993), Summer sisters (1998), Double Fudge (2002), and In the unlikely event (2015).
Other papers include awards, clippings, photographs, printed material, research and subject files, and material relating to public appearances and events, such as interviews, speeches, and book and promotional tours. Audiovisual materials in the collection appear to document Blume's public appearances.
Adolescence -- Fiction; American literature -- 20th Century; American literature -- 21st century; Authors, American -- 20th century -- Archives; Authors, American -- 21st century -- Archives; Children's literature, American; Young adult fiction, American; Born digital; Photographic prints; Sound recordings; Video recordings; Authors -- United States -- 20th Century; Authors -- United States -- 21st century
- October 2017 Acquisition, 1952-2017; 117.75; (125 boxes) + 1 roll
  Arrangement
  Organized into three subgroupings: I. Key West Material, 1952-2017. II. Glenn Horowitz Bookseller Office Material, 1956-2001. III. October 2017 Addition, 1961-2017.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Boxes 6, 92-103 (audiovisual material): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  Boxes 23, 104-105, 119 (born digital): Restricted fragile material. Access copies of digital files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - Key West Material, 1961-2015; 99.62; (106 boxes)
    Material has been left in the order in which it was received by the library.
    Scope and Contents
    The largest component of the October 2017 Acquisition is from Judy Blume's residence in Key West, Florida. The Key West materials include correspondence, drafts and proofs of writings, research and subject files, professional papers, printed material, personal papers, photographs, audiovisual materials, and born-digital (electronic) files.
    Drafts, proofs, and other materials can be found for numerous books by Blume, and in some cases multiple drafts can be found for individual tiles, including: Double Fudge (2002), Summer sisters (1998), Deenie (1973), Tiger eyes (1981), and In the unlikely event (2015).
    - Double Fudge, "2nd draft and some 3rd draft", 2001 December (Box 1)
    - Double Fudge, "third draft...", 2001 December (Box 1)
    - Double Fudge, "4th draft", 2002 January 1 (Box 1)
    - Double Fudge, "various from later drafts", 2001–2002 (Box 1)
    - Double Fudge, "Fudge outlines", 2001, undated (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous material, 2001-2002, undated (Box 1)
    - Notebooks, undated; 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Double Fudge, "revised pages", 2002, undated (Box 1)
    - Double Fudge, [part of "revised pages"?], 2002, undated (Box 1)
    - Double Fudge, "July 17-01 #2 draft", 2001 July 17 (Box 1)
    - Double Fudge, "early drafts…", 2001 (Box 1)
    - Double Fudge, "copy from working manuscript", 2001 January 20 (Box 1)
    - Double Fudge, draft, 2002 January 15 (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous material, 1998-2001, undated (Box 1)
    - Just as long as we're together, setting copy, corrected, with proofreaders' marks and printer's annotations, 1987; 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Just as long as we're together, page proof, corrected, with proofreaders' marks and printer's annotations, 1987; 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Double Fudge, "2nd draft" (empty folder), 2001 (Box 2)
    - Double Fudge, page proof, "2nd pass", 2002 May 10 (Box 2)
    - Double Fudge, page proof, "3rd pass", 2002 June 6 (Box 2)
    - Double Fudge, page proof, 2002 November 4 (Box 2)
    - Double Fudge, book jackets, undated (Box 2)
    - Double Fudge papers, 2001-2002, undated (Box 2)
    - "Deenie: A screenplay," drafts, 1987-1988, undated; 7 folders (Box 2)
    - "Deenie: A screenplay," miscellaneous pages, 1987-1988, undated (Box 2)
    - Summer sisters, draft, 1997 October 17; 2 folders (Box 3)
    - Summer sisters, miscellaneous material, 1997, undated (Box 3)
    - Summer sisters, draft pages, outlines, and notes, 1995–1996; 4 folders (Box 3)
    - Summer sisters, draft, "Fall-'95", 1995; 2 folders (Box 3)
    - Summer sisters, "notes and manuscript pages spring and summer 1996", 3 folders (Box 3)
    - Summer sisters, draft, 1995–1996 (Box 3)
    - "Articles about JB and reviews…", circa 1970s-1990s; 34 folders (Box 4)
    - "Articles about JB and reviews…", circa 1970s-1990s; 35 folders (Box 5)
    - "Love's a hard game to play," draft, 1997 March; 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Summer sisters, draft, "Up to July from notebook", 1997 July; 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Summer sisters, "Vineyard draft, June - Aug. 14, 1997", 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Summer sisters, draft, 1997 August 13; 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Summer sisters, draft, 1997 September 3; 3 folders (Box 7)
    - Summer sisters, draft, "Part Two", 1997 (Box 7)
    - Miscellaneous material, 1997-2002, undated; 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Printed material, 1969-1984, undated; 25 folders (Box 8)
    - Printed material, 1984 October (Box 39)
    - Deenie, printed versions, annotated, 1973; 2 folders (Box 9)
    - "Deenie: A screenplay by Judy Blume", 1988 January 4 (Box 9)
    - " Deenie letters…", 2004 March (Box 9)
    - "Disney ' Deenie ' list of writers", 2003-2005, undated (Box 9)
    - " Deenie screenplay 2004," notes and outlines, 2004, undated (Box 9)
    - " Deenie: A screenplay," notes and drafts, 2004-2005, undated; 2 folders (Box 9)
    - " Deenie: A screenplay," notes and drafts, undated; 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Notebook, [2005?] (Box 9)
    - " Deenie: A screenplay by Pamela Gray… first draft", 2005 January 26 (Box 9)
    - " Deenie: A screenplay by Pamela Gray… first draft," corrected, undated (Box 9)
    - " Deenie: A screenplay by Pamela Gray… first draft", 2005 February 3 (Box 9)
    - " Deenie: A screenplay, 'Larry's draft'", [2005?] April (Box 9)
    - " Deenie ," draft "by Mare Contrare", undated (Box 9)
    - " Deenie: A screenplay," "April 28 JB draft", no year April 28 (Box 9)
    - " Deenie: A screenplay," draft, corrected and annotated, undated (Box 9)
    - Miscellaneous material, 2004-2005, undated; 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Printed material, 2005, undated (Box 9)
    - "Correspondence, miscellaneous '82", 1981–1982; 2 folders (Box 10)
    - "Correspondence, routine '82", 1982; 2 folders (Box 10)
    - "Fan mail before 1979, originals", circa 1975-1978, undated (Box 10)
    - "To be filed", circa 1980-1983 (Box 10)
    - "Recent fan mail 83", 1982-1983, undated (Box 10)
    - Correspondence, 1981–1982 (Box 10)
    - "Censorship", 1980-1982,udated (Box 10)
    - "Friendship", 1980-1982, undated (Box 10)
    - "Center for Population Options", 1989-1990, undated (Box 10)
    - "High Bridge Elementary School…", 1989 (Box 10)
    - "Correspondence/requests: speaking engagements/accepts", 1989–1990 (Box 10)
    - "Awards", 1986–1990; 5 folders (Box 10)
    - The Pain and the great one material, 1984-1985, undated (Box 10)
    - Fabric, undated (Box 10)
    - "Book of letters in JB comp", 1989 (Box 10)
    - "Book of letters 2 letter & response", 1987-1993, undated; 3 folders (Box 10)
    - "Pocket books - letters", 1992 (Box 11)
    - Correspondence, 1987-1991, undated (Box 11)
    - "Book of letters 2", 1994, undated; 6 folders (Box 11)
    - " Deenie - handicaps", undated (Box 11)
    - Letters to Judy (photocopies), undated; 3 folders (Box 11)
    - "Original letters from kids", 1978-1984, undated; 2 folders (Box 11)
    - "Letters #1-112…" (photocopies), undated (Box 11)
    - "Letters #113-202" (photocopies), undated (Box 11)
    - "Letters 203-281" (photocopies), undated (Box 11)
    - "#282-369" (photocopies), undated (Box 11)
    - "Letters #370-471" (photocopies), undated (Box 11)
    - "#472-" (photocopies), undated (Box 12)
    - "Correspondence: Lorrie Kim (open)", 1978–1983 (Box 12)
    - "Families in crises", undated (Box 12)
    - "Books as bridges", undated (Box 12)
    - "Books as friends", undated (Box 12)
    - "Out of control chapter…", undated (Box 12)
    - Letters to Judy, printed version, annotated, 1986 (Box 12)
    - Material removed from Letters to Judy, printed version, annotated, undated (Box 12)
    - Box list, 1999 October 6 (Box 12)
    - "Fan mail/bad language", circa 1981-1994 (Box 12)
    - Here's to you, Rachel Robinson, "bad language", 1994–1997 (Box 12)
    - "Fan mail/child abuse", 1993 (Box 12)
    - "Fan mail/depression", 1987-1988, undated (Box 12)
    - "Fan mail/disabilities/illness", 1990-1994, undated (Box 12)
    - "Fan mail/divorce & stepfamilies", 1994 (Box 12)
    - "Fan mail/eating disorders", 1987–1989 (Box 12)
    - "Fan mail/homosexuality", 1988-1991, undated (Box 12)
    - "Fan mail/masturbation", undated (Box 12)
    - "Fan mail/sexual abuse", 1988–1990 (Box 12)
    - "Book of letters/resources", circa 1990s (Box 12)
    - "Fan mail/note to teacher regarding grades", 1982-1991, undated (Box 12)
    - "Advice letters", 1991–1993 (Box 12)
    - "Fan mail/adults 1988-", 1988–1995 (Box 12)
    - "Trash letters (requests for items [f]rom JB trash can)", 1984 (Box 12)
    - "Fan mail/letters to Judy/adults 1990" (Box 12)
    - "Adults: positive ideas and comments", 1979–1986 (Box 12)
    - "Fan mail/suicide related", 1987–1990 (Box 12)
    - "Weird: (open)", 1979–1993 (Box 12)
    - "Fan mail/scoliosis", 1983-1994, undated (Box 12)
    - Fan mail, 1979–1989 (Box 12)
    - "Death/loss", 1988–1990 (Box 12)
    - " Forever - negative", 1976-1989, undated (Box 12)
    - " Forever - positive", 1982–1996 (Box 12)
    - "Fan mail - Fudge ", 1991–1995; 2 folders (Box 13)
    - Here's to you, Rachel Robinson, "Fan mail", 1993–1995 (Box 13)
    - "Fan mail/ Letters to Judy ", 1990–1991 (Box 13)
    - "Fan mail - Tiger Eyes ", 1983–1994 (Box 13)
    - "Canada", 1986–1991 (Box 13)
    - "Australia/UK", 1990-1991, undated (Box 13)
    - "Foreign: other places", circa 1980-1991 (Box 13)
    - "Letters to excerpt", circa 1986-1994 (Box 13)
    - "Fan mail - various 1988-1990", 1987-1997, undated (Box 13)
    - "Special fan mail - '97-'98", 1995–1998 (Box 13)
    - "Fan mail Just as long as we're together ", circa 1989-1993 (Box 13)
    - "Corresp/requests - college elementary education majors", circa 1986-1997 (Box 13)
    - Box list, 1998 April (Box 13)
    - "Anna Chirinos", 1989–1991 (Box 13)
    - "Fan mail - special Wendy", 1984–1987 (Box 13)
    - "Gilana Gelman", 1988–1993 (Box 13)
    - "Fan mail - special Lorrie Kim", 1984–1993 (Box 13)
    - "Fan mail - special letters Karen McCulloch, 1984-", 1984–1995 (Box 14)
    - "Tracy Patton", 1987–1993 (Box 14)
    - "Brooke Romano", 1992 (Box 14)
    - "FM/special - Robbin Rosner", 1985–1991 (Box 14)
    - "Inbal Sharoni", 1990–1991 (Box 14)
    - "Dianna Wolf", 1986–1993 (Box 14)
    - "Wendy Wong", 1989–1991 (Box 14)
    - "Jody Baca", 1984–1987 (Box 14)
    - "Wendy Baca", 1987 (Box 14)
    - "Special kids", 1993–1994 (Box 14)
    - "Fan mail - various, 1991-1993", circa 1991-1993; 6 folders (Box 14)
    - "Fan mail - favorite books", 1995 August 15 (Box 14)
    - "Special fans…", 1994–1995; 2 folders (Box 14)
    - "Jessica Stevens Bond", 1992, undated (Box 14)
    - Fan mail, 1996, undated (Box 14)
    - "Fudge TV scripts…", 1994 (Box 15)
    - "Fudge TV series…", 1994-1995, undated; 5 folders (Box 15)
    - Notebooks, undated; 3 folders (Box 15)
    - Miscellaneous material, 1987, undated; 2 folders (Box 15)
    - Just as long as we're together, "Judy Blume's notes…", 1989 (Box 15)
    - Notebooks, 1984, undated; 2 folders (Box 15)
    - "Subrights", 1986–1991 (Box 15)
    - "Tales of a Fourth Grade Nothing," script, "by Bruce Mason", undated (Box 15)
    - "Just as - development notes", 1999, undated (Box 15)
    - Outlines, 1994 September (Box 15)
    - "[?] notes sent to Amblin", 1994, undated (Box 15)
    - "Ideas: for books, etc.", 1988-1991, undated (Box 15)
    - Notebook, 1987; 2 folders (Box 15)
    - Untitled folder, 1989–1990 (Box 15)
    - "Foxboro deal", 1989–1992 (Box 16)
    - "Just as long/Foxboro negotiations - to April 19, 1991", 1990-1991, undated (Box 16)
    - "'Just as long as we're together' (TV series, publicity)", 1989 September (Box 16)
    - Financial records, 1990–1991 (Box 16)
    - Just as long as we're together, legal records, 1991–1993 (Box 16)
    - "The Judy Blume CD-ROM companion", 1990 February 2 (Box 16)
    - Miscellaneous material, 1989–1991 (Box 16)
    - "Legal information", undated (Box 16)
    - "Printouts for TV project", 1987, undated (Box 16)
    - "Notes on 'letters' TV special, 1987", circa 1987 (Box 16)
    - "Notes + ideas on TV project", circa 1987 (Box 16)
    - "More letters - TV project", circa 1987 (Box 16)
    - "Info for NBC letter show", 1987, undated (Box 16)
    - "TV project - current", 1987, undated (Box 16)
    - "Scherick, Edgar: 1977 project", 1989 (Box 16)
    - "The Three of us," original treatment, undated (Box 16)
    - "Connections", 1989, undated (Box 16)
    - "Barr films: The Pain and the Great One", 1988-1990, undated (Box 16)
    - "Barr films: Otherwise known as Sheila the great", 1988–1993 (Box 16)
    - "Kim I", undated (Box 16)
    - "Negative letters…", circa 1975-1983 (Box 16)
    - "Orig. forms - ltrs book", undated (Box 16)
    - [Letter book?], undated; 5 folders (Box 16)
    - [Letter book?], undated; 2 folders (Box 17)
    - "Special letters - 1983 - office copies", undated (Box 17)
    - "Special letters - 1984 - office copies", undated; 3 folders (Box 17)
    - "Fan mail", 1976-1983, undated; 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Wifey, fan mail, 1978-1982, undated (Box 17)
    - "More letters to copy (copied done)", 1979-1983, undated (Box 17)
    - Forever, fan mail, 1979-1982, undated (Box 17)
    - "From parents, various", 1980–1982 (Box 17)
    - "From teachers, various", 1980–1982 (Box 17)
    - "Diary", 1980-1982, undated (Box 17)
    - Deenie, fan mail, 1980–1982 (Box 17)
    - Blubber, fan mail, 1980-1982, undated (Box 17)
    - Then again, maybe I won't, fan mail, 1981–1982 (Box 17)
    - "From librarians, various", 1982, undated (Box 17)
    - "Death", 1981-1983, undated (Box 17)
    - "Humorous", 1980-1982, undated (Box 17)
    - "Depression & suicide", 1982 (Box 17)
    - "Writings", 1980-1982, undated (Box 17)
    - "Siblings", 1981–1982 (Box 17)
    - "Divorce & stepparents", 1980-1982, undated (Box 17)
    - "Adoption", 1982 October 13 (Box 17)
    - "Boys", 1980-1982, undated (Box 17)
    - "Miscellaneous", 1980-1983, undated (Box 17)
    - "Scoliosis & other diseases", 1981-1982, udated (Box 17)
    - "Sexuality & development", 1979-1982, undated (Box 17)
    - Box list, 1998 April (Box 18)
    - "Invitations to speak", 1987–1990 (Box 18)
    - Tales of a fourth grade nothing, stage adaptations, 1987–1992 (Box 18)
    - "Rosenfeld, Bernie", 1993–1995 (Box 18)
    - "AASL meeting, April 1996", 1995–1996 (Box 18)
    - "SCBWI 1995 Roster", circa 1995 (Box 18)
    - "Correspondence: requests [for] personal appearance-regrets", circa 1993-1998 (Box 18)
    - "Correspondence: speaking engagements - regrets", 1993–1997 (Box 18)
    - Miscellaneous material, 1995 (Box 18)
    - "Correspondence: Harvard School of Public Health", 1995–1996 (Box 18)
    - "Motion Picture Association of America, 1996", 1992–1996 (Box 18)
    - "School Board Election, 1993" (Box 18)
    - "PEN - annual benefit, Monday, April 13, 1992", 1991–1993 (Box 18)
    - "PEN American Center", 1983–1995 (Box 18)
    - "People for the American Way", 1991–1992 (Box 18)
    - "SCBWI corres. 1983-95", 1983–1995 (Box 18)
    - "SCBWI parties, 1992, 1994, 1995", 1992–1995; 3 folders (Box 18)
    - "The Scoliosis Association", 1991–1992 (Box 18)
    - "Starbright Foundation", 1992-1994, undated (Box 18)
    - "Summer house 1991, Vineyard Haven, Martha's Viney" (Box 18)
    - "Testimony: Colorado case 1982", 1982–1983 (Box 18)
    - Trumpet Club correspondence, 1991-1997, undated (Box 18)
    - "KF contributions 2003 8.3", 1999-2000, undated (Box 18)
    - "KF contributions 2005" (Box 18)
    - "Professional correspondence 2005", 2000-2005, undated (Box 18)
    - Summer sisters, drafts, 1997–1998; 14 folders (Box 19)
    - Last night never happened, drafts, undated; 4 folders (Box 19)
    - Tiger eyes, drafts and notes, 1980-1982, undated; 13 folders (Box 20)
    - "Keogh Plan", 1982 August; 2 folders (Box 20)
    - Last night never happened, draft, "May 1996", 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Last night never happened, draft, "July 1996", 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Last night never happened, draft, "Nov-Dec 1996", 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Last night never happened, draft, "Dec 1996", 1996–1997; 3 folders (Box 21)
    - Last night never happened, draft, "Late Fall/Winter 1996-97", 1996–1997; 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Last night never happened, "mishmash manuscript pages with many notes + changes, Fall 1996", 2 folders (Box 21)
    - "'Threesome' pilot - March 5, 1991", 1991 March 5 (Box 22)
    - "'Threesome' Act Two - rev", 1991 March 4 (Box 22)
    - "'Threesome,' pitch info/family histories, 1989, undated (Box 22)
    - "'Dragons'/Larry's comments", 1991 April 26 (Box 22)
    - "Queen of mean", 1989, undated (Box 22)
    - "Flings", 1989, undated (Box 22)
    - "Thanks a lot", 1989, undated (Box 22)
    - "Secrets", 1989, undated (Box 22)
    - "Sharing", 1989, undated (Box 22)
    - "Fame", 1989, undated (Box 22)
    - "Hunks", 1989, undated (Box 22)
    - "Episode notes", undated (Box 22)
    - Friends, 1989, undated (Box 22)
    - "Threesome", 1989, undated (Box 22)
    - "Pefect", 1989, undated (Box 22)
    - "Notes from meeting with Longstreet", 1989, undated (Box 22)
    - notebook, undated (Box 22)
    - Just as long as we're together, notes, 1988, undated; 3 folders (Box 22)
    - Just as long as we're together, drafts, 1991 April (Box 22)
    - "Nelle's original pitch, story lines, + characters", 1989 September (Box 22)
    - "'Dragons' (Just as pilot) 4/29/91)", 1991 April (Box 22)
    - "Archival copy of Just as long as we're togther ver. 3/5/91 Initial submission to Lifetime Network", 1991 March 5 (Box 22)
    - Just as long as we're together, "Judy Blume blue notebook April-June 1989" (Box 22)
    - "Rachel's book chapters", 1991 November (Box 22)
    - Miscellaneous notes, 1991 February 26 (Box 22)
    - "Series - notes", 1988-1991, undated (Box 22)
    - Miscellaneous ephemera, undated (Box 22)
    - Just as long as we're together, "notes on 1/2 series", 1990, undated (Box 22)
    - Just as long as we're together, "Book 2 - TV series", undated (Box 22)
    - Just as long as we're together, notes, 1989-1991, undated (Box 22)
    - Just as long as we're together, "First budget", 1991 April 29 (Box 22)
    - "July 26, 1991 revised script as sent to Nelle", 1991 July 26 (Box 22)
    - "April 29, 1991 as sub. to network", undated (Box 22)
    - Electronic media, 1991, undated; 1 mini-Floppy disk, 2 2.5" disks, 2 digitized microfilm CDs (Box 23)
      Box 23 (digital media): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - "Longstreet pilot", 1991 January 18 (Box 24)
    - "Feb 15, 1991 as sent to Nelle", 1991 February 15 (Box 24)
    - "Feb 13/14 1991 notes + Renee as typist", 1991 February (Box 24)
    - "Rachel's chapters - spring 1989", undated (Box 24)
    - "JB draft #1 after receiving longstreet draft", undated (Box 24)